rapidfeeds.com 2006-12-18

# Privacy Policy - RapidFeeds

RapidFeeds is committed to protecting your online privacy while providing you with the most useful and efficient service possible. We respect your privacy and are committed towards keeping your personal information safe. 

How we collect and use personal information

Registering for membership on RapidFeeds gives you access to all of the site�s services. The only information required is your name and e-mail address. With your approval, we occasionally will send e-mail to notify you about important changes to the site, new services, important upgrades and special offers from us. If you would rather not receive these e-mail notifications, then please use the instructions on the bottom of the e-mail to unsubscribe. RapidFeeds uses the best technology around in preserving your personal information, to prevent unauthorized use of your e-mail address. 

How we protect your personal information

All personal data you enter on RapidFeeds is secure with the same state-of-the-art security software we use to guard all of our company�s essential business data. In addition to using the most secure technology available, we work tirelessly to make sure that we use any information you provide us only in ways you have approved. 

How we use "cookies"

As you probably know, "cookies" are small pieces of information that some Web sites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit them. Like many other Web sites, RapidFeeds uses cookies to identify members so they don�t have to enter a user ID and password upon each visit. You can select the �remember my password� option, which remembers your password for up to 2 weeks. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to modify security settings so you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis. Even if you do not use cookies, you can still access all of the features on our site by logging in manually with each visit. 

Obtaining your consent

By using our Web site, you give RapidFeeds permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. If you register at RapidFeeds, you authorize RapidFeeds to use information you provide to personalize the information we deliver to you and to use your demographic information when calculating aggregate customer data. As a registered member, you give RapidFeeds permission to send you e-mails related to our website and partnering sites. RapidFeeds will not sell or rent your email address to anyone without your consent. If you are under the age of 13 you must not provide your name, e-mail address, or any other identifying information without the consent of your parent or guardian, or as otherwise provided for by applicable law. Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

Tell us what you think

RapidFeeds welcomes your questions and comments about our privacy policy. Please send e-mail to [**feedback@rapidfeeds.com**](mailto:feedback@rapidfeeds.com) or **click here** to contact Us.
